Liones Kingdom
Imperial Capital Liones
One Month Ago
(騎士･回想)
((ここを お開けください！))
Please open the door!
You have nowhere else to run!
(騎士)
((もう逃げ場はございませんぞ))
King!
(騎士)((国王！))
(国王)((エリザベス 逃げなさい))
You must escape, Elizabeth.
I won't go alone! You must get to safety as well!
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)((一人は嫌です！
お父様も ご一緒に))
Your father will be fine.
(国王)((父は大丈夫だ))
((でも…))
But!
(国王)((聖騎士たちが来る前に))
Go now, before the Holy Knights get inside.
((≫(騎士たち)うおぉ～～！))
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)＜聖騎士たちによる
クーデターで城を追われた➡
Due to the coup d'état by the Holy Knights,
リオネス王国 第三王女
エリザベスは➡
The third princess of the
Liones Kingdom, Elizabeth,
窮状を脱するべく 伝説の逆賊➡
fled in distress and began her journey
七つの大罪を捜す旅に出た＞
in search of the Seven Deadly Sins.
How is it?
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)どうだ？
おいしい｡
Delicious...
＜ だが その道行きは厳しく➡
However, her journey was fraught with peril.
Before long, she almost ended up captured.
ついに 捕らわれの身となるかに
思われたが➡
But then a certain person appeared to save her.
そこに
救いの手を差し伸べる者がいた＞
This person was the captain of the Seven Deadly Sins,
＜彼こそが 七つの大罪が団長➡
The Dragon's Wrath, Meliodas!
憤怒の罪のメリオダス
その人であった＞
There, she met her savior!
The Seven Deadly Sins
<
Dragon's Wrath
Meliodas
＜ これは いまだ
人と 人ならざるものの世界が➡
This is a tale of humans
and beings from other worlds.
分かたれてはいなかった
古の物語＞
It is a story of ancient times.
＜国を守る聖騎士たちは
絶大なる魔力を有し➡
The Holy Knights who protected this country
wielded immensely powerful magic.
恐れ 敬われた＞
They were both feared and revered.
＜ だが その中で 国を裏切り➡
However,
a faction arose who betrayed their country and turned their blades against the remaining Knights.
全聖騎士を
敵に回した者たちがいた＞
To the masses, they were known as the "Seven Deadly Sins."
＜人々は
彼らを 七つの大罪と呼んだ＞
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
I run through my unwavering thoughts
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume ni tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
I run through my emotions of giving up
akirameru omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume ni tsunai da kimi to
≫エリザベス｡
あっ はい｡
Elizabeth!
Y-Yes?
Take a look outside.
ちょっと 下 下りてきてくれ｡
はい｡
Okay!
This isn't a dream!
(心の声)≪夢じゃない｡
私 本当に見つけたんだ➡
I've really found one!
あの伝説の 七つの大罪の一人
メリオダス様を≫
The legendary member of the Seven Deadly Sins.
Lord Meliodas!
≪たぶん…≫
I think...
あの… この服装は？
うちの制服だ｡
Um... About this outfit...
It's my bar's uniform.
Sorry that his taste is so obvious.
(ﾎｰｸ)こいつの趣味
丸出しで悪ぃけどな｡
So, all I have to do is gather rumors and information on the Seven Deadly Sins
ウエイトレスをしながら
七つの大罪に関する噂や情報を➡
お客さんから
集めればいいんですよね？
while I wait on customers, right?
Information on the Holy
Knights would be helpful too.
聖騎士に
関することでもいいぞ｡ ふむ｡
きゃあ！
安心しろ ただのサイズチェｯクだ｡
Don't worry, just making sure it's nice and snug.
Idiot! We just got some eye candy in
here and you're gonna drive her away?!
バッキャロ～！ せっかくの
看板娘が 逃げちまうだろ！
Episode 2
Sword of the Holy Knight
あの… メリオダス様
一つお聞きしたいことがあります｡
Lord Meliodas, there's just one question I wish to ask you.
ん？
七つの大罪は…➡
The Seven Deadly Sins...
メリオダス様は
本当に 世間が言うような➡
Lord Meliodas, are you as evil as the rumors say you are?
大罪人なのでしょうか？
If you are, what crime did you
commit to earn your reputation?
だとすれば
どんな罪を犯したのでしょうか？
What crime did I commit...
どんな罪… か｡
私は 何か
世間が誤解していると思うんです｡
I just feel like there must be some
sort of misunderstanding here.
Because you saved me! Someone you barely know.
だって あなたは
正体の知れなかった私を➡
助けてくれた｡
実は…➡
Well...
Ten years ago, I traveled all around Liones and stole all the women's underwear I could find.
１０年前 リオネス各地で
女性の下着という下着を➡
盗んで回ったんだ｡
う… うそですよね!?
Y-You're kidding, right?!
うそ｡
うっ…｡
Yep.
Actually, I went around groping
the breasts of over 1,000 women.
実は 1000人以上のねえちゃんの➡
おっぱいというおっぱいを
もんで歩いたんだ｡
Wh-What? Are you joking?!
ぱ… ぱい!?
じょ… 冗談ですよね!?
Yep.
冗談｡
うっ！
Please stop making fun of me!
ちゃかさないでください！
それとも➡
Or did you really commit a crime that you can't speak about to anyone?
本当に人には言えないような罪を
犯したんですか？
まあな｡
あっ…｡
Something like that.
きゃあ！
おっと 危ない！
Whoa, watch out!
こらこら！
(ﾎｰｸﾏﾏ)ブゴ～ッ！
Hey, hey!
着いたか｡ 次の情報の仕入れ先➡
Here we are.
Our next target for gathering information.
バーニャの村だ｡
Bernia Village!
うちの酒は いろんな土地で
仕入れてるんだが➡
My bar stocks alcohol from all over the kingdom,
バーニャの酒は別格だ｡
but the booze from Bernia is on a different level.
Using water from a river hailed as the best in all of Liones
リオネス屈指とうたわれる名水と
その川辺に群生する➡
and grout that's found growing along the banks, Bernia Ale is renowned throughout the kingdom.
グルートから作る
バーニャエールは➡
各地に ファンがいるんだ｡
でもよ
その名水が すっからかんじゃんよ｡
But...
it appears that the famous river has dried up.
The herbs all look like they've wilted too.
川辺のハーブも枯れてますね｡
どういうこった？
What could've happened?
うわぁ～！
人が たくさん集まってますね｡
There are so many people here!
お祭りでしょうか？
I wonder if there's a festival?
Yo!
おい～っす｡
(村人)おっ おお…➡
｢豚の帽子｣亭の｡
今日は なんの祭りだ？
You're the Boar Hat's—
Is there a festival today?
Huh? Does this look like a festival to you?
はあ!? これが祭りに見えるか！➡
We're trying to pull out the sword that the Holy Knight stuck into the ground!
聖騎士様が突き立てた剣を
引き抜こうとしてんだよ！
The Holy Knight stuck the sword?
聖騎士が剣を？ なんでまた？
Why'd he do that?
(村長)先日 聖騎士様の
怒りを買ってしもうてな｡➡
Yesterday, we incurred the wrath of a Holy Knight.
その方の魔力を帯びた剣が➡
The Holy Knight's magic-imbued sword
村の地下水全体を
封じてしまったんじゃ｡
has sealed away the village's underground water source.
At this rate, not only will the river disappear, but all the grout, too!
このままじゃ 水だけじゃなく
グルートも全滅しちまう｡
If that happens, Bernia's ale will be...
そうなれば
バーニャのエールは…｡ くそっ！
Dammit!
聖騎士って まさか
あのメリオダス様が倒した…｡
A Holy Knight...
It couldn't be the one that Lord Meliodas defeated, could it?
You mean Lord Twigo?
あのツイーゴってヤツのことか？
あいつは
聖騎士なんかじゃねぇぞ｡
He wasn't really a Holy Knight.
えっ？
つぅか本物は あんなもんじゃねぇ｡
A real one is nothing like that.
(村長)聖騎士様の剣を
引き抜けるとしたら➡
If a Holy Knight stuck the sword into the ground, only a Holy Knight could pull it out.
聖騎士様のお力しかない｡
It pains me to say this,
村の者には言いにくいが➡
but this village is finished.
この村は もう おしまいじゃよ｡
そんな…｡
But...
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)あぁ～あ！ みんなして
何 情けねぇ声 出してんだよ｡
Oh, come on, what's everyone whining about?
ミード！
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)聖騎士の突っ立てた剣が➡
Mead!
What's with the commotion about this Holy Knight's sword?
なんだってんだ！➡
If you leave it to my pal from the
Seven Deadly Sins, it'll be a breeze.
俺のダチの七つの大罪にかかりゃ
そんなん楽勝だぜ｡
これっ ミード！
一体 誰のせいで➡
Listen, Mead!
Just who do you think is responsible for this in the first place?
こんな目に遭ってると
思ってるんだい！
Mentioning the Deadly Sins is just
about the worst thing you could do!
言うに事欠いて
大罪人の名を口にするなんて！
Yeah! Don't make the Holy
Knight angrier than he already is!
そうだ！ 聖騎士様を
これ以上 怒らせないでくれ｡
俺たちに
なんの恨みがあるってんだい！
What exactly do you have against us?!
Wh-What?!
な… んだよ｡
俺は そんなつもりじゃ…｡
I never meant it like that.
お前のうそと いたずらには
もう つきあえん！
We're through with your lies and jokes!
Stupid Mead!
ミードのバカ！
ガン！
I hate you all!
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)ふんだ！ みんな 大嫌いだ！
俺たちだって
ミードのことが大嫌いだよ！
Yeah, well, we all hate you too, Mead!
Shut up you idiots! Idiots!
うるせぇ！ バ～カ バ～カ！
なんで 俺まで｡
Why am I getting dragged into this?
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)バ～カ！
(村長)みんな やめんか！
Everyone, stop!
なんだか 厄介なときに
来ちまったみてぇだぜ｡
Looks like we dropped by at a bad time.
He's a good kid deep down, but...
あれも 根は
素直で 真面目な子なんですが…｡
Man, that was horrible.
やれやれ｡
とんだ目に遭ったもんだ｡
Hey, kid.
なあ ガキんちょ｡ さっきの…｡
お前だって ガキじゃねぇかよ｡
Back there...
Aren't you a kid too?
俺は ガキではないのだ｡
I ain't no kid.
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)ここって酒場？
Is this... a bar?
｢豚の帽子｣亭｡ 俺の店だ｡
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)腹減った｡
The Boar Hat.
It's my bar.
I'm hungry.
Well, answer my question
and I'll cook you something.
質問に答えたら 飯食わしてやる｡
飯が先｡
んん…｡
Food first.
It looks delicious! Time to eat!
うっまそ～！ いただきま～す！
まずっ！
うまい飯とは言ってねぇぞ｡
Disgusting!
I never said it would be good.
で ほんとなのか？
So...
Is it true?
That your friend is one of the Seven?
お前の友達が
七つの大罪って話は｡
The food was so disgusting that I forgot.
まずすぎて忘れた｡
That smell... It's Bernia Ale, right?
この匂い バーニャエールだろ？➡
Wait, you're a kid, so you shouldn't really be drinking that.
あれ？ でも お前
ガキのくせに飲んでいいのかよ？
Like I said, I ain't no kid.
だから 俺 ガキじゃねぇし｡
I-It tastes amazing, right?!
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)そ… それ うまいだろ？
ふっ｡
ああ｡
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)甘みとコクの強い➡
Yeah.
The sweet and rich taste makes it the best ale!
最高のエールなんだ！
って… 大人が言ってた｡
≫カラン カラン(ﾄﾞｱﾍﾞﾙ)
Or that's what the adults told me, anyway...
Oh, you're back.
おお 二人とも｡
バタン｡
ミードちゃん あなた
相当ないたずらっ子だそうですね｡
Mead, you're quite the prankster, aren't you?
The Village Chief told me everything.
村長さんに聞きましたよ｡
Huh? What's with this meddling lady?
なんだよ なれなれしい女だな｡
ふふっ｡ 私も
小さいころ よくいたずらして➡
When I was younger, my father used to
scold me all the time for pulling pranks.
父に叱られました｡
ふん！ それがどうした｡
What's your point?
I wanted his attention.
気を引きたかったんです
本当の父じゃなかったから｡
Because he wasn't my real father.
一度
庭にあった大きな木に登って➡
One time, I climbed the big tree in our garden
to try to give him a fright.
父を びっくりさせようと
したことがあって｡
However, my father's face turned pale, and he began to climb up after me.
そしたら 父が 真っ青になって
木を登ってきたんです｡
一度も 木に登ったことも
ないような人が…｡
He had never climbed a tree before.
案の定 父は 木から落ちて
軽いケガをしてしまいました｡
As expected, he couldn't climb it,
fell down, and was injured.
私 あのときのことが
今でも忘れられないんです｡
I...
can't forget what happened, even now.
If my father had died back then...
もし あのとき
父が死んでしまっていたら…｡
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)俺だって そんなつもりで
うそとか言ってんじゃ…｡
I...
didn't mean to pull pranks or tell lies because of that.
話して｡
Tell me.
M-My...
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)
お… 俺の父ちゃんと母ちゃんは➡
mom and dad were both travelers.
旅人だったんだ｡ でも 二人とも➡
But a few years ago, they both fell victim to an epidemic when they stopped by Bernia Village.
数年前
バーニャの村に立ち寄ったとき➡
はやり病で死んじまった｡➡
独りぼっちになった俺を
村のみんなが➡
I was alone...
But the villagers took me in and
raised me in place of my parents.
親代わりに育ててくれた｡➡
I was really happy.
俺 すごくうれしかったんだ｡➡
でも やっぱり
俺は 誰の家族でもなくて…｡
But in the end, I was never a part of anyone's family.
I became jealous of everyone else who had families.
本当の家族がいるみんなが
羨ましくて➡
うそついたり いたずらしたり…｡
Started pulling pranks and telling lies...
Is that why you put the bug in the Holy Knight's drink?
聖騎士のお酒に
虫を入れたのも 同じ理由？
No! It was because that Holy
Knight made fools out of all of us!
違う！ それは あの聖騎士が
みんなをバカにしやがったからだ！
(村長)((今年は 村の全員が
最高の出来と自負しております))
This year's ale is the best batch we've ever made.
It's our pride and joy.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)((まずい))
(一同)((あっ…))
Disgusting.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)
((馬の小便よりは マシな程度だ))
It's only slightly better than a horse's urine.
((ひ… ひあっ！))
(村長)((お… お許しくだされ))
N-No!
Please forgive us!
All the adults and even the kids
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)いい酒を造るために
大人も子供も➡
worked hard every single day to make the very best ale.
毎日 毎日 手間暇かけて…｡
それを あいつは！➡
But he...
Holy Knights are all a joke!
聖騎士なんて ろくでなしだ｡
So, when you said your friend was one of the Seven...
じゃあ 七つの大罪が
お前の友達って話は？
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)う… うそ｡
I-It was a lie...
I see. Got worked up for nothing.
そっか｡
ちょっとは期待したんだがなぁ｡
Why make up a lie like that?
でも どうして そんなうそを？
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)だって 七つの大罪は
聖騎士に追われてるんだろ？
Because the Seven Deadly Sins are
being chased by the Holy Knights, right?
If the evil Holy Knights are after them,
悪い聖騎士に追われてるなら➡
that means they must be good people, right?
七つの大罪は
いいヤツってことだろ？
あっ｡
プゴッ｡
何？
ふふっ｡
Hmm?
≫(村人たち)おい！
(３人)ん？
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)村の方からだ｡
It's coming from the village.
Mead!
ミードちゃん！
ん？
(騎士)クズどもが！ よく聞け！➡
Listen up, you scum!
日没までに
聖騎士様の剣を引き抜かねば➡
If you aren't able to pull out the
Holy Knight's sword by sunset,
村人に課す取り立てを
今までの１０倍にする！
we're going to increase the
taxes on this village tenfold!
That's insane!
(村人)むちゃくちゃだ！
(村人)水がかれたままじゃ➡
Forget about being paid tenfold.
１０倍どころか
１本分の酒も造れねぇよ！
With the water dried up, we won't even be able to make a single glass of ale!
(騎士)これは罰だ｡
聖騎士様を侮辱しただけでなく➡
This is your punishment!
Not only did you insult the Holy Knight,
大罪人 七つの大罪を
友などと のたまったからだ｡
you even claimed that one of the villainous Seven Deadly Sins was a friend of yours!
Shit, if only Mead hadn't shot his stupid mouth off!
くそっ！ ミードが
バカなことさえしなければ｡
ミード！
また お前か｡
Mead?!
Not you again.
ガキじゃ
面白くもなんともねぇんだよ｡
It's boring to watch
a brat like you try all the time.
取り立て ２０倍にすんぞ～？
Soon the taxes'll be twenty times as high!
There's no way you'll be able to pull it out.
お前なんかに
抜けるわけないだろ！
Idiot!
これ以上 俺たちを困らせるな！
Stop embarrassing us even further!
≪(村長)いいかげんにせい！
Enough of this!
Village Chief...
(村人)村長…｡
Who was it that insulted our pride as ale brewers?
わしら酒造りの誇りを
傷つけたのは誰じゃ？➡
Was it Mead?
ミードか？ 違うぞ｡➡
No!
That child said what we were all feeling, did he not?
あの子の行為は
いつだって わしらの気持ちの➡
代弁だったのではないか？
あっ おばさん｡
村長さんの言うとおりだ｡
A-Auntie?
It's as the Village Chief says.
What you did was not wrong.
悪いのは あんたじゃない｡
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)あっ｡
お～い！ おめぇら
俺たちの話 聞いてたか？➡
Hey, did you fools not hear what we said earlier?
It's going to be twenty times more, twenty!
２０倍だぞ ２０倍！
女子供は どいてな｡
ミード｡
Women should stand back.
Mead.
All right, let's do this!
よし いくぞ！
(２人)ははははっ！
ぴくりとも動かねぇでやんの｡
It's not even moving an inch!
We're gonna sit back and watch you
fools while we enjoy your cheap beer.
俺たちゃ
貴様らの安酒で飲み直しだ～｡
抜けろ！
Come on!
抜けろ～～‼
Come out, goddammit!
(２人)あはははっ！
見ろ！ あの必死な顔｡
Look at their desperate faces!
A toast, to these fools!
バカどもに乾杯… あっ｡
酒の味が分からんヤツらに➡
People who don't appreciate the taste
of alcohol don't deserve to drink this ale.
この酒を飲む資格はねぇよ｡
(一同)うわっ！
≪ドォーン！(人が倒れる音)
(一同)ごほっ ごほっ ごほっ…｡
ごちそうさん｡
ん？
That hit the spot.
悪いけど
今 持ち合わせ ねぇからさ➡
Sorry, but I don't have anything on me to pay you with.
これでいいか？
So how's this instead?
(騎士)バ バ… バカな！➡
No way!
A sword that only a Holy Knight can pull out...
聖騎士様にしか抜けない剣を➡
あ… あんなガキが｡
ゴゴゴゴゴッ(地響き)
was taken by a kid?!
(２人)あっ！
なんの音だ？
What's that sound?
ドッバーン！
(２人)ぎゃあ～！
水だ！
はははっ！
(２人)ごほっ ごほっ…｡
忘れ物だ｡
(２人)ああっ！
You forgot something.
≪やっぱり すごい≫
Amazing...
≪これが 七つの大罪の力≫
So this is the strength of one of the Seven.
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)ねえ にいちゃんは
ひょっとしたら 本当に…｡
Hey, could you possibly be the real...
Yep.
おう！ ひょっとしなくても➡
Not just "possibly."
I'm the real, proud owner of a bar!
俺は
ただの立派な酒場のマスターだ｡
That's not what I meant!
そうじゃなくて…｡
それよか➡
Besides,
お前にゃ
やることが残ってんだろ？
you still have something you need to do, right?
(村長)ミード すまなかった｡
Mead,
we're really sorry.
わしたちを許してはくれないか｡
Can you forgive us?
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)
ゆ… 許すとか許さねぇとか…｡➡
Whether or not I forgive you...
別に 俺は一人だって…｡
For someone who's alone like me...
行け｡
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)な… なんだよ!? 行けって｡
Come on.
Wh-What do you mean, "Come on"?
I... don't get what you're saying...
意味分かん… ねぇ｡
(村人)ミード｡
Mead.
Mead!
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)うぅ… ううっ…｡
(おばさん)ミード｡
Mead!
うわぁ～～ん！
どんなうそついたって
自分の心だけは だませねぇんだぜ｡
No matter what lies you tell,
you can't fool your own heart.
(村人たち)ははははっ！
(村人)｢豚の帽子｣亭 メリオダス➡
To Boar Hat's Meliodas!
かんぱ～い！
わ… 私に➡
Cheers!
I...
I wonder if I'll be able to pull this off.
うまくできるでしょうか？
こういうことをするのは
初めてなので➡
It's the first time I've ever done anything like this.
ドキドキしています｡
I'm so nervous.
I see, I see. So this is your first time.
そうか そうか 初めてか｡
Can you say that one more time? Just once more.
もっかい言ってみ もっかい｡
何に興奮してんだ
てめぇは！
What are you getting all excited for?!
まっ 今日は
情報を得るとか考えずに➡
Well, don't worry about gathering information today.
ウエイトレスに集中していいから｡
Just focus on being a waitress for now.
At any rate, you should take it easy for now.
何はともあれ 気楽にやってくれ｡
Y-Yes!
はっ はい！ 気楽にいきます！
I'll take it easy!
≪きゃあ！
≪バシャン！
Sorry! I'm really sorry!
ごめんなさい！
本当に ごめんなさい！
えっ 頼んでない？
You didn't order this?
But...
あれ？
こっち こっち｡
Hey, over here!
あっ はい｡ きゃあ～！
Yes!
うみゅ～…｡
こりゃ
残飯には 事欠かなそうだぜ｡
Well, looks like we'll have plenty of leftovers.
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)
ねえちゃん うちの手伝いとか➡
Lady, you've never helped
out at home before, have you?
したことねぇだろ？
ドキッ！
I can tell just by looking.
見てて分かんだよなぁ
全然 なってねぇもん｡
You've never done a chore in your life.
Stop it, Mead. Acting all high and mighty.
こらっ ミード！
偉そうなこと言って｡
あんたは もっと反省しな｡
You need to reflect on your actions more.
If you get too cocky, we'll throw you into the Forest of White Dreams.
あんまり調子に乗ってたら
白夢の森に放り込んじゃうよ｡
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)ええっ!? やだ！
白夢の森って？
Not that!
Forest of White Dreams?
A forest even the powerful Holy Knights avoid!
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)聖騎士も近寄らない
おっかない森なんだ｡➡
おばさん いい子にするから
それだけは許してよ｡
Auntie, I'll be a good boy, so please forgive me!
(おばさん)
ほんとかねぇ？ この子は｡
This kid is just...
(ﾐｰﾄﾞ)約束するって！
(おばさん)おばさんの目➡
I promise!
Don't even try to fool this auntie. I'm keeping a close eye on you!
ごまかそうったって
ちゃ～んと見てるからね｡
Approximately 7 Miles Southeast of Bernia Village
Fort Solgales
(ｶｲﾙ)さ… 先ほど➡
E-Earlier...
We received a report from
the soldiers at Bernia Village.
バーニャの村 駐留の兵より
報告があり➡
しょ… 正体不明の子供が➡
A-An unidentified child has...
その… ギルサンダー様の剣を
引き抜いたと｡
pulled out Lord Gilthunder's sword!
(ｶｲﾙ)きっと
何かの偶然で その子供が…｡
I'm sure it's by chance that the child—
Are you suggesting that a Holy Knight's sword was pulled from the ground by "chance"?
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)偶然で 聖騎士の刺した
剣が引き抜けるとでも？
N-No, sir, but...
(ｶｲﾙ)い… いえ 決して｡
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)バーニャへの距離と
方角を教えてくれ 正確にな｡
Give me the direction and distance to Bernia.
Make sure it's accurate.
(ｶｲﾙ)はっ？ あっ はい！
この砦より 南東４時の方向｡➡
Yes, sir!
From this fort, it is four o'clock to the southeast,
距離にして ７.３マイル｡
7.3 miles away.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)
君のその槍 貸してもらえるな？
That spear of yours...
Can I borrow it?
(衛兵)はあ｡ どうぞ｡
Of course.
This angle, I guess.
(ｷﾞﾙｻﾝﾀﾞｰ)この角度か｡
ふん！
いいのか？ 王女様
出てっちまったぜ｡
Is this gonna work out?
She's a mess out there.
Aren't you gonna console her or anything?
慰めに行ってやんのか？
んん～？ 小便だ｡
Going to pee.
ったく 頼りねぇ店長だぜ｡
Man, what an unreliable owner.
この店は
俺の肩ロースに懸かってんな｡
This bar's really riding on my pork shoulders.
メリオダス様｡
おう｡
Lord Meliodas...
Yo.
I'm sorry.
すみません
まだ仕事の途中なのに｡
I know we're in the middle of business,
but after seeing Mead and everyone else,
I was reminded of Father and me.
ミードちゃんたちを見てたら 急に
父のことを思い出してしまって｡
そうか｡
無事だといいけど｡
I see.
I hope he's safe.
ここら辺りかな｡
ダメですね➡
Around here... I think...
I'm useless, right?
This is the wrong time to get homesick, isn't it?
ホームシックに
浸っている場合じゃないのに｡
もうちょい左か？
A little more to the right?
The people suffering under the
oppression of the Holy Knights...
聖騎士の横暴に
苦しめられている人たちが➡
There are still so many of them.
まだ たくさんいるのに
王女が こんなことじゃ➡
With me being so useless...
先が思いやられますね｡
I'm scared to think about what lies ahead.
でも 俺を見つけたろ｡
あっ… えっ？
But you found me, right?
お前が
みんなを守りたいと思って➡
If you didn't have the determination to protect the people,
俺の店に たどりつかなかったら
何も始まらなかった｡
and to find my bar while
you could barely even walk,
none of this would've started.
This is something I have to do for myself.
私には やるべきことがある…｡
Exactly.
そゆこと｡
I have something I've gotta do for myself, too.
俺には俺の やるべきことがある｡
Lord Meliodas!
メリオダス様～！
ほい！
ドドォーン！
(部下)何があった!?
(部下)団長！ カイル団長！
(ｶｲﾙ)
ギルサンダー様 ご無事ですか!?➡
Lord Gilthunder!
Are you okay?
ギルサン… あっ！
Gilth—
やはり生きていたか 七つの大罪➡
You were alive after all...
The Seven Deadly Sins'...
メリオダス｡
Meliodas!
メリオダス様！
ドンドコドコドコ…｡
Lord Meliodas!
Lord Meliodas! Just now, was that the same Holy Knight who attacked the village?
メリオダス様！ 今のは まさか➡
村を襲った聖騎士の？
たぶんな｡ こりゃ さっさと
村を出た方がよさそうだ｡
Probably.
I think it'd be best for
everyone if we left this village.
でも
もし また ここが狙われたら…｡
But what if they attack this village again?
It'll be much more dangerous if we stay here.
俺たちがとどまってる方が
よっぽど危険だ｡
Do we even have a place to hide?
どっか隠れる場所でもありゃな｡
Come to think of it...
そういえば…｡
どうした？
What's up?
Earlier, Mead said that the Forest of White
Dreams is a place where we should never go.
さっき
ミードちゃんが 白夢の森だけは➡
絶対 行きたくないって｡
Even the Holy Knights refuse to enter.
なんでも
聖騎士が避けて通る森だって｡
おあつらえ向きじゃねぇか｡
That's the perfect place, then!
決まりだな｡
でも 隠れるんじゃねぇぞ｡
Guess it's decided.
However, we're not going there to hide.
We're going to do what we set out to do.
俺たちがやるべきことをやる｡
What are you talking about?
どういうこった？
あっ｡
What we must do...
まさか…｡
ああ｡ たぶん➡
Yup.
There's probably another one there.
そこに一人いる｡
あっ！
行こう！ ｢七つの大罪｣捜しだ！
Let's go!
To search for our friends!
Yes!
はい！
We're going back and forth on a dead-end street, yo
itta ki tari de ikidomari yo
This abandoned dream is a bitter experience, yo
mihatenu yume wa kori gori kori gori yo
After all, this world we live in is transient, yo
shosen konoyo wa ukiyo no sekai
Open up and renew yourself to find high spirits, yo
hirakinaoreba NORINORINORINORI yo
High spirits, yo!
NORINORI yo
Throw in the firewood to reignite
maki wo kubero tayasu na sono hi wo
Your blazing passion before it goes out
tsuki ugokasu MONO wa sou kandou sa
The future will be fine as long as it shines brightly
mirai wa tada kagayaite kurete ireba ii’nda
We switched our intense rampage on
bokura wa Gan Gan abare MO-DO
Making seven sounds of thunder
todorokasu Boom Boom nanatsu no oto
Heading toward an ever-bright tomorrow
Rin Rin hikaru ashita e to susumou
We're ready to shoot the place up
bokura wa Bang Bang Haji ke MO-DO
Jumping here and there as we go
buttobasu Ran Dom SUTAIRU de ikou yo
Shining through like a diamond
Bling Bling hikaru DAIYAMONDO
Let's go, now we can fly high
iku ze Now we can fly high
Next Episode's Report
Elizabeth's costume has changed!
＜エリザベスの
コスチュームがチェンジした＞
However, neither her strength nor defense have changed!
＜ だが 戦闘力も防御力も
何も変わらない＞
＜ いや むしろ下がった！＞
No, if anything, they've decreased!
お色気とかが ２くらい
アップしてるんじゃないの？
But her sex appeal has gone up, hasn't it?
いや そこは
前のｺｽﾁｭｰﾑの方がいいって人も…｡
Nah, I think her previous outfit was better.
お前の好みで
この服になったんだろ！
Isn't her outfit like this
because of your preferences?!
でも こっちも捨て難い｡
もうボロボロじゃねぇか！
It's hard to throw this away though.
That one's all tattered!
それもまた 一興｡
This one is fun too!
Enough of this!
いいかげんにしろ！
(ﾎｰｸ ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)うわっ！
Next week
on "The Seven Deadly Sins."
次回 『七つの大罪』
｢眠れる森の罪｣｡
The Sin of the Sleeping Forest.
Don't play around with a person's clothing, please!
人の服で 遊ばないでください！
Episode 3
Sin of the Sleeping Forest
大型で強い台風１９号が
東シナ海を北上している｡
台風は今後､進路を東寄りに変えて
九州南部に接近し､